&gt；&gt；steve kinney：所以另一个问题，或者另一个解决方案，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So the other problem,
or the other solution,
这就是我们需要发送一些东西的时候，是的，让浏览器去获取它。
to this is when we need to send something,
yes, have the browser go get it.
但是如果我们可以让浏览器不问我们东西，并且
But if we can have the browser
not ask us for stuff, and
只是利用它已经有的东西，那会更快，对吧？
just use the stuff it already has,
that's gonna be faster, right?
因此，实现这一点的一种方法是利用HTTP缓存。
And so a way to do that is
to make use of HTTP caching.
所以想象一下，这一年是1997年。
So imagine for
a second that the year is 1997.
那年我们收到了很多很棒的礼物。
We received a lot of
great gifts that year.
我们收到了“泡芙爸爸”和“家庭无路”。
We received Puff Daddy and
the Family's No Way Out.
我们还接收到HTTP/1.1中的Cache-Control响应头。
We also received Cache-Control
response headers in HTTP/1.1.
可以说，其中一个比另一个产生了更大的影响。
Arguably one of those had more
of an impact than the other.
我将把它作为练习留给观众去找出哪一个更多
I'll leave it as an exercise to the viewer
to figure out which one of those was more
对我的童年发展很重要。
important in my childhood development.
但是，是的，我们有这些Cache-Control响应头，我们放进去了。
But yeah, we've got these Cache-Control
response headers, that we put.
你要求的东西，我们发给你了，
You asked for something,
we sent it to you,
我们有一些标题，可以为您提供一些有关它的额外信息。
we have some headers that give you a
little bit of extra information about it.
缓存并不能解决所有问题。
And caching is not gonna do everything.
你发送一个POST或PUT，这些就像，嘿，在服务器上改变这个数据。
You send a post or a put, those are like,
hey, change this data on the server.
我们不缓存那些。
We don't cache those.
但是，嘿，你想要这个资源，
But hey, you want this resource,
你想要这只猫GIF，你想要这个JavaScript文件？
you want this cat GIF,
you want this JavaScript file?
CSS文件？
The CSS file?
就像，如果你已经有了，就用你现有的，不要问我
Like, if you already have it just use
the one you have, don't ask me for
又一个。
another one.
因为我要把这东西带到地球的另一端。
Cuz I gotta get the thing
half way around the world.
这根管子只有这么大，它在漏水，它是有问题的。
This pipe is only so big,
it's leaking, it's problematic.
因此，可以对这些HTTP方法进行缓存、GET、Options和Head。
So these HTTP methods can be cached,
Get, Options, and Head.
一堆其他的改变服务器上的东西，
A bunch of other ones that
change stuff on the server,
你不会想要缓存它们，对吧，就像你不想让它们更新一样。
you wouldn't want them cached, right,
like you wouldn't want them updating.
像缓存这样的东西，你想让它去服务器，所以有点道理。
Something like cache, you want that to
go to the server, so kinda makes sense.
还有一堆不同的设置。
And there's a bunch of
difference settings.
我们不会谈论太多不可变的，
We're not gonna talk too
much about immutable,
因为我相信现在只有Firefox支持它，
because I believe right now
it's only supported in Firefox,
不是其余的浏览器，但我们将讨论前四个浏览器。
not the rest of the browsers, but
we will talk about these first four.
因此，想象一下使用浏览器缓存时，我们所处的环境之一
So imagine with browser
cache that we're in one of
任意给定点的三个条件。
three conditions at any given point.
我们没有把它放在缓存里，这很容易。
We don't have it in cache, that's easy.
如果缓存中没有它，请转到服务器并
If you don't have it in cache,
go to the server and
明白了，对，这就说得通了。
get it, right, that makes sense.
陈旧的，这是检查，但让我们看看你是否有。
Stale, which is check but
let's see if you have.
你在缓存中有一些东西，但它已经过期了。
You have something in cache but
it's out of date.
对，你需要新的。
Right, you need the new one.
并且有效，也就是你在缓存中有这个。
And valid which is you have this in cache.
这是正确的。
It's the right one.
别跟电视网说话。
Don't talk to the network.
就用你现有的吧。
Just use the one you have.
我们都知道
And we all know that
不与服务器交谈将比与服务器交谈更快。
not talking to a server is going to
be faster than talking to a server.
我们知道金科玉律，对吧？
We understand the golden rules, right?
就像跳过整个，让我问问服务器。
Like skipping the entire,
let me ask the server.
让我获取这些TCP数据包。
Let me get these TCP packets.
那些东西一遍又一遍。
All that stuff over and
over and over again.
不这样做会更快。
It is going to be faster to not do that.
在一个非常简单的Express服务器中，您可以调整其中的每一个，
In a very simple express server
you could tweak each one of these,
从无存储到缓存缺失或
from no-store to cache missing or
no-store到no-cache to max-age，依此类推。
no-store to no-cache to max-age,
and so on and so forth.
每一个都试一试。
Try each of these out.
没有商店，就像不商店一样。
No-store which is like don't store.
和你想的一模一样，对吧？
It's exactly what you think it is, right?
像浏览器一样，每次都去获取一个新版本。
Like browser,
go get a new version every time.
这可能是，您可能希望您的HTML页面使用此功能，对吗？
This could be, you might want this for
your HTML page, right?
特别是如果它是一个客户端设置，只是指向一些bundle。
Especially if it's a client setup
that's just pointing at some bundles.
不，我需要你看看这个的新版本是什么。
No, I need you to see what
the new version of this one is.
我更新了这个。
I updated this.
请去获取HTML页面。
Please go get the HTML page.
no-cache意味着您可以存储副本，但是
No-cache means you can store a copy, but
至少和我核实一下，看看你有没有最新的版本。
at least check with me to see if
you have the most recent version.
它将执行我们称为条件GET的操作，
It will do what we call a conditional get,
嘿，有这个版本，这个版本对吗？
hey, have this version,
is this the right version?
对，这是有代价的，因为你仍然需要检查。
Right, there's a cost to that,
because you still need to check.
但如果服务器运行是的，那就是正确的版本，
But if the server goes yeah,
that's the right version,
那么它就不需要给你发那个文件了。
then it doesn't need
to send you that file.
另一个是max-age，你会说，听着，我刚刚发送的这个文件
And the other one is max-age, which you
say like, listen, this file I just sent
你，下一秒不管它是有效的，只要相信它，对吧。
you, for the next however many seconds
it's valid, just trust it, right.
不要问我，就像也许十分钟后你可以再问我一次，一年，随便什么。
Don't ask me, like maybe in a ten minutes
you can ask me again, a year, whatever.
我们可以做这些事情中的任何一件，因为缓存很棒，除非它搞砸了
We can do any of those things because
caching is great unless it messes
向上，对吗？
up, right?
我们可以说，缓存很长时间，然后我们发布一些糟糕的JavaScript文件。
We can say, cache this for a long time,
and then we ship some bad JavaScript file.
我们想要某种破解宝藏的方法。
We wanna have some kind
ofway of busting the cache.
因为否则我们可以说，浏览器，保留这个损坏的JavaScript文件
Because otherwise we can say, browser,
hold on to this broken JavaScript file and
永远不要再向我要一个。
never ask me for another one.
这就是所谓的不再是客户[笑]对吗？
That's called no longer
a customer [LAUGH] right?
这叫做放弃你的用户。
That's called a user who
has given up on you.
那可不好。
That's not great.
并且用户必须进行我们称为硬刷新的操作，
And the user would have to do
what we call a hard refresh,
这在每个浏览器中都有一点不同。
which is a little bit
different in every browser.
但这不是刷新。
But it's not a refresh.
它涉及到按住Shift或
It involves holding shift or
敲击其他键的鸡尾酒来清理缓存并做一些事情。
hitting some other cocktail of keys
to clear out the cache and do stuff.
你知道谁会这么做吗？
And you know who's gonna do that?
没有你的用户。
None of your users.
你的用户都不会是，你知道吗？
None of your users are gonna be,
you know what?
我可能有一些双层缓存资产。
I've probably got some bunk cache assets.
如果我进行硬刷新呢？
What if I do a hard refresh?
[笑]没人会这么做。
[LAUGH] No one's going to do that.
我不会那么做的，对吧？
I'm not even going to do that, right?
这从来都不是一个想法
That is never a thought,
当某件事不起作用时，我就会想到这一点。
when something has not worked,
that has ever crossed my mind.
我就这么走了
I just go,
就像，还有其他东西可以让我去看看多巴胺。
like, there's something else that can
give me a dopamine hit to go look at.
我要去做那件事。
I'm gonna go do that instead.
所以有一个解决方案
So one solution for
这就是我们所说的内容可寻址存储，这是一种非常奇特的方式
this is what we call Content-Addressable
Storage, which is a very fancy way
将一堆垃圾添加到我们的文件名的末尾，对吗？
of adding a bunch of garbage to
the end of our file name, right?
它所做的是有效地重建它，我们检查一些文件，
What this does is effectively rebuild it,
we check some of the file,
我们给它一个唯一的标识符，我们说，去拿那个文件，然后
we give it a unique identifier,
and we say, go get that file, and
如果我们构建一个新版本的应用程序，什么是新的数字？
if we build a new version of our
application, what has a new number?
对，如果有人问你，你可以告诉浏览器
Right, you can tell the browser
if somebody asks you for
main.567ee7aa72b3ee48649.js，保持一年，对。
main.567ee7aa72b3ee48649.js, hold
onto that for a year, right.
我们可以把它放在我们的索引研究SMIL文件中，如果我们更新我们的应用程序，
We can put that on our index study
SMIL file and if we update our app,
我们更新了索引研究SMIL文件，我们会说，好的，这是新版本。
we updated the index study SMIL file,
we'd be like, okay here's the new version.
因此，我们有效地获得了免费的缓存破坏。
So we effectively get cache-busting for
free with that.
使用CDN也可以做一些有趣的事情，对吧？
There's some interesting things you
can do with CDNs, as well, right?
因为CDN也将缓存内容，这通常是，如果CDN，
Because the CDN will also cache stuff,
which is normally, if a CDN,
它的工作方式是你把你的酷文件放在互联网上，在云中。
the way that it works is you put your
cool file on the internet, in the Cloud.
它要么在您的服务器上，要么在S3存储桶中，或者其他什么地方。
That's either on your server, or
in an S3 bucket, or whatever.
用户去CDN，嘿CDN，你有名字吗。567eea。
The user goes to the CDN, and
hey CDN, do you have name.567eea.
我不能，我的记忆力不是很好。
I can't, my memory's not that good.
它要么拥有它，要么不拥有它。
And it will either have it or
it won't have it.
如果它没有它，它会去你的服务器并得到它，
If it doesn't have it,
it will go to your server and get it,
然后它会在世界的那个地区保存一份拷贝，所以
and then it will keep a copy of that
in that region of the world, so
下一个人要求它，他们得到了快速版本。
the next person asks for it,
they get the fast version.
所以我们可以告诉CDN，嘿，拿着这个
So we can tell the CDN,
hey, hold on to this and
给它一个最大年龄，它就会做到这一点。
give it a max-age and it will do that.
然后浏览器可以保留它，所以浏览器不会询问。
The browser can then hold on to it,
so the browser won't ask.
如果浏览器需要询问，它会去询问CDN，希望CDN有一个版本。
If the browser has to ask, it will go ask
the CDN which hopefully has a version.
我们不想用这个来永远保留一切，因为如果我们发送给他们
We don't wanna use this to hold on to
everything forever because if we send them
一个糟糕的版本我们有点穷困潦倒。
a bad version we're kind of up the creek.
但是，这个s-maxage仅用于CDN，因为如果我们发布CDN的版本不好，
But, this s-maxage is for CDNs only
because if we ship the CDN a bad version,
我们可以联系CDN，然后就像，哟，
we could reach out to that CDN and
be like, yo,
丢失那个版本，从你的缓存中清除它。
lose that version,
clear it from your caches.
因此，这是另一种不同于您在CDN上设置的最大寿命的方法。
So it's another way to have a different
max-age from what you set on the CDN.
人们只需要走到CDN与他们保留的内容之间的距离
People only have to go as far
as the CDN versus what they keep
在他们的浏览器里，对。
in their browser, right.
把这些都弄好是一门很好的艺术。
And getting these right is
a little bit of a fine art.
一般来说，如果您使用web pack或
Generally speaking, if you use web pack or
很多其他的构建工具，文件命名部分都是为您完成的。
a lot of the other build tools,
the file naming part is done for you.
对，之后通常会使用主和字符串。
Right, it'll usually use that main and
that string afterwards.
对，就是一般来说，
Right, and that is, generally speaking,
除了一些很酷的未来技术，处理它的一个很好的方法。
with barring some cool new future
technologies, a great way of handling it.
如果文件更改，它将具有不同的文件名。
If the file changes,
it will have a different file name.
因此，您可以存储，可以在服务器上设置max-age，用于
So you can store,
you can set the max-age on the server, for
很长的文件名到一年。
that very long file name to a year.
这是你能做的最大限度。
That is the maximum you can do.
听着，如果你还在要求
Listen if you are like still asking for
这个文件，对，因为对于该版本的文件来说是唯一的。
this file, right, cuz that's unique
to that version of the file.
就用你现有的，好吗？
Just use the one you have, right?
这是修复负载性能的第一步，
And that is kind of the first step
in fixing your load performances,
确保设置了缓存头。
making sure you have cache headers set.
拿着这个对吧？
Hold onto this, right?
别再问我要了。
And don't ask me for it again.
现在，对于我们作为前端工程师来说，它总是悬而未决，无论是还是
Now, for us as frontend engineers,
it's always up in the air, and whether or
不是我们能控制的，只要我不能控制那些东西，
not we control that,
wherever I don't control those things,
就像行动部门控制所有的人一样。
like the ops department
controls all of them.
我问他们，已经完成了。
I ask them, it is done.
希望，或者它还没有完成，或者其他类似的事情，对吧？
Hopefully, or it's not done, or
something along those lines, right?
但是前端工程师我们并不总是能控制这些东西。
But the frontend engineer we don't
always have control of those things.
但还有其他事情是我们可以控制的，
But there are other things
that we do have control over,
我会花更多的时间在上面，而不是像那些步骤。
that I'm gonna kinda spend a little bit
more time on, versus like those steps.
所以，是的，我们可以重申我在发货前说的，因为有一个糟糕的版本，
So yep, we can reiterate I said before
we ship because there is a bad version,
我们真的没有很好的选择。
we don't really have a great choice.
我们给CDN提供了一个不好的版本，我们不能和CDN说话。
We ship the CDN a bad version,
we can't talk to the CDN.
然而，我们不能触及每个人的所有浏览器
We can't however,
reach into all the browsers of everyone
谁曾经访问过我们的网站，因为我们推出了糟糕的版本。
who has ever accessed our websites
as we push out the bad version.
就像，哟，浏览器，清除掉。
It'd be like, yo, browser, clear that out.
网络不是这样运作的。
That's not how the web works.